# This file should contain all the record creation needed to seed the database with its default values.
# The data can then be loaded with the bin/rails db:seed command (or created alongside the database with db:setup).
#
# Examples:
#
#   movies = Movie.create([{ name: 'Star Wars' }, { name: 'Lord of the Rings' }])
#   Character.create(name: 'Luke', movie: movies.first)

questions = [
    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This?: Identity Theft Is Not A Joke, Jim!",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Michael",
            "Pam",
            "Ryan"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Sometimes I’ll start a sentence and I don’t even know where it’s going. I just hope I find it along the way.",
        correct_answer: "Michael Scott",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "David Wallace",
            "Kevin"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I talk a lot, so I’ve learned to tune myself out.",
        correct_answer: "Kelly",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jan",
            "Creed",
            "Meredith"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : Dwight mercy-killed Angela’s cat.",
        correct_answer: "Pam",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "Phyllis",
            "Jim"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : A few years ago, my family was on a safari in Africa and my cousin, Mufasa, was um, he was trampled to death by a pack of wildebeests and um, we all took it really hard.",
        correct_answer: "Ryan",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Michael",
            "Pam",
            "Ryan"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : If I don’t have some cake soon, I might die.",
        correct_answer: "Stanley",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Michael",
            "Pam",
            "Kevin"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : Guess what, I have flaws. What are they? Oh, I don’t know. I sing in the shower. Sometimes I spend too much time volunteering. Occasionally I’ll hit somebody with my car. So sue me.",
        correct_answer: "Michael Scott",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jan",
            "Angela",
            "Creed"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : The worst thing about prison was the dementors.",
        correct_answer: "Prison Mike",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Michael Scott",
            "Date Mike",
            "Ping"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : It is not a good time for me to lose my job since I have some pretty big long-term plans in my personal life with Pam that I’d like her parents to be psyched about. So, I am about to do something very bold in this job that I’ve never done before: try.",
        correct_answer: "Jim",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Roy",
            "Ryan",
            "Brian the Camera Guy"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : I’ve been involved in a number of cults, both a leader and a follower. You have more fun as a follower, but you make more money as a leader.",
        correct_answer: "Creed",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Meredith",
            "Oscar",
            "Dwight"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : News flash: You are not special.",
        correct_answer: "Stanley Hudson",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Dwight Schrute",
            "Angela Martin",
            "Jan Levinson-Gould"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I wanted to eat a pig in a blanket, in a blanket.",
        correct_answer: "Kevin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Erin",
            "Michael",
            "Andy"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I’m fast. To give you a reference point. I’m somewhere between a snake and a mongoose. And a panther.",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jim",
            "Creed",
            "Meredith"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : Tell ya one thing, I’m not gonna be a good mom tonight.",
        correct_answer: "Meredith",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Angela",
            "Jan",
            "Pam"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : When Pam gets Michael’s old chair, I get Pam’s old chair. Then I’ll have two chairs. Only one to go.",
        correct_answer: "Creed",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Kevin",
            "Gabe"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : Boy, have you done lost your mind? Cause I’ll help you find it!",
        correct_answer: "Stanley",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Dwight",
            "Darryl",
            "David Wallace"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I Am Not Superstitious, But I'm A Little 'Stitious.",
        correct_answer: "Michael Scott",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Creed",
            "Clark",
            "Pete"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Mini-Cupcakes? As In The Mini Version Of Regular Cupcakes? Which Is Already A Mini Version Of Cake? Honestly, Where Does It End With You People?",
        correct_answer: "Kevin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Robert California",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : The only problem is whenever I try to make a taco, I get too excited and crush it.",
        correct_answer: "Kevin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Clark",
            "Pete",
            "Andy"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : I’m guessing Angela is the one in the neighborhood that gives the trick-or-treaters toothbrushes, pennies, walnuts.",
        correct_answer: "Pam",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Gabe",
            "Oscar",
            "Phyllis"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : Besides having sex with men, I would say the Finer Things Club is the gayest thing about me.",
        correct_answer: "Oscar",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "Robert California",
            "Michael Scott"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : If I had to, I could clean out my desk in five seconds, and nobody would ever know that I’d ever been here. And I’d forget, too.",
        correct_answer: "Ryan",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Andy",
            "Erin"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : Who is Justice Beaver?",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jim",
            "Gabe",
            "Creed"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Sometimes I get so bored I just want to scream, and then sometimes I actually do scream. I just sort of feel out what the situation calls for.",
        correct_answer: "Kelly",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kevin",
            "Pete",
            "Andy"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I find the mystery genre disgusting. I hate being titillated.",
        correct_answer: "Angela",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Meredith",
            "Robert California",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Mini-Cupcakes? As In The Mini Version Of Regular Cupcakes? Which Is Already A Mini Version Of Cake? Honestly, Where Does It End With You People?",
        correct_answer: "Kevin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Robert California",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I say dance, they say, ‘How high?'",
        correct_answer: "Michael",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "David Wallace",
            "Robert California",
            "Jan"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : As a person who buys a lot of erotic cakes, it’s nice to be represented on one.",
        correct_answer: "Phyllis",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Meredith",
            "Pam",
            "Ryan"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I love inside jokes. I’d love to be a part of one someday.",
        correct_answer: "Michael",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Gabe",
            "Jo",
            "Kevin"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Last year, Creed asked me how to set up a blog. Wanting to protect the world from being exposed to Creed’s brain, I opened up a Word document on his computer and put an address at the top. I’ve read some of it. Even for the internet, it’s… pretty shocking.",
        correct_answer: "Ryan",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jim",
            "Clark",
            "Toby"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Ultimatums are key. Basically, nobody does anything for me anymore unless I threaten to kill myself.",
        correct_answer: "Kelly",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Phyllis",
            "Erin",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : You’re the people’s princess! Diana was nothing!",
        correct_answer: "Meredith",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Michael",
            "Dwight"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : I think it’s great that the company’s making a commercial, because not very many people have heard of us. I mean, when I tell people I work at Dunder Mifflin, they think that we sell mufflers or muffins or mittens or… and frankly, all of those sound better than paper, so I let it slide.",
        correct_answer: "Jim",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Darryl",
            "Ryan",
            "Stanley"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : I’m always thinking one step ahead, like a carpenter that makes stairs.",
        correct_answer: "Andy",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Creed",
            "Kevin",
            "Dwight"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I can’t use Phyllis! Are you kidding me? The moment she steps off this bar, I’ll be launched into space! God, you’re so insensitive.",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Creed",
            "Angela",
            "Michael"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : You Only Live Once? False. You Live Every Day. You Only Die Once.",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Creed",
            "Michael",
            "Jim"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I Wish There Was A Way To Know You’re In The Good Old Days Before You've Actually Left Them.",
        correct_answer: "Andy",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Gabe",
            "Erin"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : If I were buying my coffin, I would get one with thicker walls so you couldn’t hear the other dead people.",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jim",
            "Robert California",
            "Gabe"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : One day Michael came in and complained about a speed bump on the highway. I wonder who he ran over then.",
        correct_answer: "Jim",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Toby",
            "Oscar",
            "Meredith"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : Would I rather be feared or loved? Easy. Both. I want people to be afraid of how much they love me.",
        correct_answer: "Michael Scott",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jo Bennett",
            "Robert California",
            "Jan Levinson-Gould"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : It takes an advanced sense of humor. I don't expect everybody to understand.",
        correct_answer: "Michael",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Andy",
            "Kevin",
            "Oscar"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I got six numbers. One more would have been a complete telephone number.",
        correct_answer: "Kevin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Creed",
            "Gabe",
            "Meredith"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Sorry I annoyed you with my friendship.",
        correct_answer: "Andy",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jim",
            "Pam",
            "Kelly"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I am one of the few people who looks hot eating a cupcake.",
        correct_answer: "Kelly",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Toby",
            "Ryan",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I am aware the effect I have on women.",
        correct_answer: "Charles",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Michael",
            "Robert California",
            "Dwight"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I love catching people in the act. That's why I always whip open doors.",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Angela",
            "Phyllis",
            "Pam"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Everything I have I owe to this job. This stupid, wonderful, boring, amazing job.",
        correct_answer: "Jim",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Toby",
            "Michael",
            "Pam"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : There's something about an underdog that really inspires the unexceptional.",
        correct_answer: "Robert California",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jo Bennett",
            "Charles",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : I am so tired of the Black Eyed Peas. It's rock n roll for people who don't like rock n roll. It's rap for people who don't like rap. It's pop for peole who don't like pop.",
        correct_answer: "Robert California",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Kevin",
            "Dwight"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : In high school, I organized a walk out over standardized testing. Got over 500 students to just skip the SATs. At the last second I chickened out, took it anyway got a twelve twenty. Always regretted it... I feel lachrymose.",
        correct_answer: "Andy",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "David Wallace",
            "Darryl"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : I feel God in this Chili's tonight.",
        correct_answer: "Pam",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jim",
            "Phyllis",
            "Michael"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : Sometimes the clothes at Gap Kids are just too flashy.",
        correct_answer: "Angela",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Erin",
            "Phyllis",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : You know, I thought this was an office, not the thunderdome.",
        correct_answer: "Clark",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Pete",
            "Andy",
            "Stanley"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : You need to access your uncrazy side, otherwise maybe this thing has run its course.",
        correct_answer: "Darryl",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Ryan",
            "Creed"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : Everyone I know who skis is dead.",
        correct_answer: "D'Angelo",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Jo Bennett",
            "Robert California",
            "David Wallace"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : My last job was at a Taco Bell Express. But then it became a full Taco Bell and, I don't know, I couldn't keep up.",
        correct_answer: "Erin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "Kelly",
            "Andy"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : You don't want to get on my bad side, I have seen some horrible things, I own over 200 horror movies.",
        correct_answer: "Gabe",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Pete",
            "Clark",
            "Creed"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : He answers to Michael. Michael G. Scott. Michael J. Fox. Mr. Fox. The Incredible Mr. Fox.",
        correct_answer: "Holly",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Michael",
            "Dwight",
            "Kevin"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : My psychiatrist thinks that I have some self-destructive tendencies, and that for once, I should indulge them.",
        correct_answer: "Jan",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Oscar",
            "Pam",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : I’m a breast cancer survivor, close, personal friends with Nancy Pelosi, and Truman Capote and I slept with three of the same guys.",
        correct_answer: "Jo Bennett",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "D'Angelo",
            "Phyllis",
            "Nellie"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : I have one simple philosophy in business: if the seat is open, the job is open. It's how I came to briefly race a Formula One car. The three slowest laps ever recorded.",
        correct_answer: "Nellie",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Kelly",
            "Jo Bennett",
            "Robert California"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : It just occurred to me that Andy has been calling me Plop for so long, he forgot my real name. Which is...",
        correct_answer: "Pete",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Clark",
            "Gabe",
            "Dwight"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : Hazing is a fun way to show a new employee that she is not welcome or liked.",
        correct_answer: "Toby",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Dwight",
            "Jim",
            "Ryan"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Life is short. Drive fast and leave a sexy corpse. That’s one of my mottos.",
        correct_answer: "Stanley",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "Kevin",
            "Kelly"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 3,
        question: "Who Said This? : The Taliban is the worst. Great heroin though.",
        correct_answer: "Creed",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Ryan",
            "Robert California",
            "D'Angelo"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 1,
        question: "Who Said This? : Why are all these people here? There’s too many people on this earth. We need a new plague.",
        correct_answer: "Dwight",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Pam",
            "Creed",
            "Gabe"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Holly is ruining Michael’s life. He thinks she is so special, and she’s so not. Her personality is like a 3. Her sense of humor is a 2. Her ears are like a 7 and a 4. Add it all up and what do you get? 16. And he treats her like she’s a perfect 40. It’s nuts.",
        correct_answer: "Erin",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Meredith",
            "Pam",
            "Phyllis"
        ]
    },

    {
        difficulty: 2,
        question: "Who Said This? : Every so often, Jim dies of boredom.",
        correct_answer: "Pam",
        incorrect_answers: [
            "Oscar",
            "Karen",
            "Kelly"
        ]
    }
]

questions.each do |question|
    q = Question.create(content: question[:question], difficulty: question[:difficulty])
    q.answers.create(content: question[:correct_answer], correct: true)
    question[:incorrect_answers].each do |answer| 
        q.answers.create(content: answer, correct: false)
    end
end

users = [
    {name: 'Not Jim', score: 30},
    {name: 'Phyllis Lapin-Vance', score: 35},
    {name: 'Pamela Beesly', score: 100},
    {name: 'Kevin', score: 1},
    {name: 'Kelly', score: 25},
    {name: 'DWIGHT AND THIS GAME IS STUPID', score: 14},
    {name: 'Michael Gary Scott', score: 29},
    {name: 'Oscar M', score: 20},
    {name: 'Ryan', score: 7},
    {name: 'Meredith', score: 12}
]

User.create(users)